effectiveeducators.com 2015-03-19

# Learning Sciences International Privacy Policy

By entering or using The Learning Sciences International ("Learning Sciences") website(s), you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth in the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

All information submitted to LearningAccount.net, a service of Learning Sciences International, is private and held in confidence. We will carefully protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration. In addition, we will not sell, rent, trade, or give away personal information to other companies for use in selling products or services.

This website contains links to other sites. Learning Sciences is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. We recommend that you refer to each website's privacy policy before giving out any personal information on their site.

## Why We Collect Information

As a provider of complete online educational services, Learning Sciences needs to collect and store certain personal information from its users for several reasons. Learning Sciences must know who each member is, have proof of their identity, know how to contact them, and, occasionally, verify how the member is using the site. Details of the users' identities are necessary to verify that the participants using the site are legitimate. Financial information is used only to bill the user.

Personal information is required for registration, to log your use of the site, and when applicable, to log your progression through the courses and grant credit. If at any time, information you submit can be viewed publicly, we will inform you how it will be used. There will also be a direct link to this policy to make our intentions clear.

## How We Collect Information

Learning Sciences primarily collects information through the registration and purchase screens. We use "cookie" technology to enable certain functions. Cookies are used to gather non-personal information, such as progress tracking.

## How We Protect Information

We offer the use of a secure server. The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all the data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

## How We Update Information

How We Update Information You may update or change information related to your account by accessing your account with your username and password. If you have any other questions please contact Customer Service at [cs@iObservation.com](mailto:cs@iObservation.com).

## Public Forums

There are discussion groups held within the site. Please be aware that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information for users in the site and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information.

## E-mail Communication

We do not rent or sell addresses to third parties for unsolicited communications.

## Spamming

You must agree that you will not utilize e-mail addresses presented on the website to transmit unsolicited messages.

## Security

Learning Sciences has security measures that protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of information under our control. The site requires a username and password combination to utilize all features. Information is stored in a secured database accessible only by Learning Sciences International. The site has been designed to allow users to view only the information that they have been permitted to view. For example, users can only view information within courses in which they are enrolled. Learning Sciences International constantly monitors sites for unauthorized usage.

## Credit Card Security

Online transactions with a credit card are safeguarded with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. There is no external access to the information. Learning Sciences International will strictly monitor the information internally. If any fraudulent activity occurs, Learning Sciences International will notify you immediately.

## Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Learning Sciences International. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Contact Us

If you have any other questions regarding the privacy policy, please contact Customer Service at [cs@iObservation.com](mailto:cs@iObservation.com).
